{
	"records":[
		{
			"question":"2 x 5 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 2 =",
			"answer":6
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 5 =",
			"answer":50
		},
		{
			"question":"0 x 2 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 4 =",
			"answer":8
		},
		{
			"question":"3 x 5 =",
			"answer":15
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 6 =",
			"answer":12
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 8 = ",
			"answer":80
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 5 =",
			"answer":5
		},
		{
			"question":"8 x 2 =",
			"answer":16
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 6 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 5 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 2 =",
			"answer":4
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 2 =",
			"answer":20
		},
		{
			"question":"2 x 9 = ",
			"answer":18
		},
		{
			"question":"4 x 10 =",
			"answer":40
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 9 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 2 =",
			"answer":2
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 3 =",
			"answer":30
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 2 =",
			"answer":14
		},
		{
			"question":"0 x 10 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 5 =",
			"answer":5
		},
		{
			"question":"10 x 10 =",
			"answer":100
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 5 =",
			"answer":25
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 9 =",
			"answer":45
		},
		{
			"question":"7 x 5 = ",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"0 x 5 =",
			"answer":0
		},
		{
			"question":"1 x 10 =",
			"answer":10
		},
		{
			"question":"5 x 7 = ",
			"answer":35
		},
		{
			"question":"57 x 10 = ",
			"answer":570
		}
	]
}





























